Is it possible to sell $100 million worth of books
and break the Guinness World Record
for the biggest launch ever?
Well, on August 16th of 2025, I tried and this would happen.
So after doing some research,
I figured out who the record holders were
for the best-selling non-fiction launch of all time.
And they were literally presidents, monarchs,
and politicians.
And since we're trying to do something
that no one else has ever done before,
I knew I had to do work that no one had ever done before.
So step one was I actually wrote the book.
That was the easiest part.
This was my third book in the $100 million series.
First, you write your offer,
then you advertise your offer,
and then you monetize your offer.
Step two is you make the offers.
So we created 17 different things
in order to actually accompany the book
to make it even more valuable.
Step three is make value-added bonuses.
So I made a 24-chapter secret playbook
and 12 playbooks that were 600 pages in total.
Step four is marketing assets.
So I wrote 10 different landing pages, six VSLs,
400 pages of email and text copy,
1,700 slides for the presentation, and over 3,000 ads.
Step five, damage control.
So we took backup plans for all potential choke points.
Number one, if we got suspended from an advertising platform,
our Google Ads account got down.
Emails and text not going through with the link to go live,
the live link not working, payment processing not working.
Our Shopify link was sending people to Serbia.
Step six, we trained the sales team.
So we pulled the salespeople and non-salespeople,
and we trained them on the book launch offer
so that they could handle the phones.
And we had 700 people who were handling the phones
over three days.
Number seven, set up and prep.
So we built our set in the headquarters
rather than doing it in a vendor.
I practiced the presentation.
I can't even tell you how many times,
but literally, at what point am I gonna move this book?
And I had to be able to talk and move at the same time,
and believe me, the first times, it sucked.
Step eight was the actual event itself.
Everybody, everybody quiet on set.
We're going live in five, four, three.
I'm Alex Samosi, and welcome to my $100 million
Money Models book launch event.
So just a few hours into the event,
we sold 1.4 million copies and broke
the Guinness World Record.
And so we went live on Friday, Saturday, and Sunday,
over those 72 hours and sold 3.6 million copies
that generated $106 million in sales.
If you like this kind of stuff,
follow to see whatever crazy thing we do next,
because it will be even crazier.